Gah! What the hell happened?
Eww. They're covered in moldy stains!
How could this happen?
It must be because of
that leak in the ceiling.
Oh crap.
Like, aren't we screwed?
The festival is the day after tomorrow!
Let's just throw them all
in the washing machine and—
No, don't do that!
If you don't clean the stains
and mold before washing,
I don't think you'll ever get them out.
Then what can we do?
I'll treat the stains
and then wash them all myself!
Will you make it in time?
Maybe if I stay up all night.
I know you need these
garments for the festival, so...
You can count on Kinme!
Wash It
All Away
Episode 5 I Have a Feeling...
Kinme Cleaning
Right behind you.
Okay.
Start
Pause
I went ahead and put the ones
that were ready in the washer.
Thank you very much.
Sure. I'll take the ones
that have been washed upstairs.
I really appreciate you
staying so late to help out.
Are you all going to be okay
for school tomorrow?
Oh, sure. We'll be totally fine.
But I mean, do you still have a lot
of work to do to get the mold out?
Yes, it seems so.
Potassium
One round of stain removal
isn't cutting it.
Mold is composed mostly of
organic ingredients,
so I apply a neutral detergent at
13% concentration directly to the mold
and then spray it out.
But after that,
there's still some discoloration,
so I have to oxygen-bleach that out
and try all sorts of treatments.
Jeez. And you have
to do them all one by one?
Yes, the stains are different
for each one.
I have to keep that in consideration when
deciding how much detergent to apply.
Serious? How annoying!
Yes, it is. But as annoying as it can be,
when I think about what I'm restoring
and all the festival memories
these outfits hold for people,
I'm happy to do it.
I'm going to do a little more
and then take a break myself,
so when you're done with those,
go ahead and call it a night.
Please tell the boys they can go too.
Yes, ma'am!
Kinme-san sure does love cleaning.
Meanwhile, this one here...
is sleeping on the job.
What a little baby.
Kinme-san, I... made a delicious
midnight... snack for you.
Festival
'Sup. Making progress?
Huh? Yeah.
'Kay, here's the last of 'em.
Kinme-san said she'd handle the rest,
so we can go home.
How's she doing?
She's still working on the mold stains.
I knew this would've been
difficult for her alone.
But I mean, what is
Kinme-san's story anyway?
Huh?
Like, wasn't this place
abandoned for years?
And I don't think Kinme-san
is from around here.
Oh.
Yeah, I think she said she moved
to Atami two years ago.
Hmm, really? Just to open a cleaning shop?
Dunno. She didn't say why.
My memory only goes back two years.
It seems I washed
all my older memories clean away.
So you don't know either, huh.
Anyway, I'm pooped.
I'm gonna head home
and get some sleep. Good night.
Yeah.
Kinme-san! We're taking off.
Oh, should we come back to help tomorrow?
I think I can handle the rest
by myself. Thank you, though.
Sorry about my dumb brother.
He made rice but didn't put
anything together to eat.
Oh, it's fine.
But thank you for everything today.
It really helped!
Kuriru-chan really does act
like the older one.
I mean, for a boy, you are so scrawny.
I'd better get some rest
before I wear myself out too.
You should probably start
heading home, Kyusho-kun.
I'll hang up the rest myself.
Actually, this is the last one.
Good. Finished.
She has to treat stains, wash,
hang clothes to dry, and then iron them,
while also making pickups and deliveries?
Cleaning is a lot more
labor-intensive than I thought.
Oh, I'm all done, Kinme-san.
Oh shoot! I must have dozed off!
The lights are off.
Has Kyusho-kun already left?
Yeah, he might have
caught me sleeping again.
Please don't work too hard
Start
Pause
We Pick Up and Deliver!
Kinme Cleaning
Festival
Just in time.
Welcome.
When I talked to her,
she said they were all ready to go,
so I thought we should come
and help her carry them, but...
Is she even here?
Kinme-san, are you in?
What a messy sleeper.
By the way, I wanted
to apologize about yesterday.
I was gonna cook up
a midnight snack but fell asleep.
Oh, it's all right.
I ended up falling asleep myself.
And Kyusho-kun saw
how sloppily I sleep again.
Hi, everyone.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Wow, you can't tell
that they were moldy at all!
Thanks, Kinme-san.
Talk about professional work!
They look brand new.
My pleasure.
Seriously, thank you, though.
Kyu told me how much work it was.
It's all thanks to them.
I never would've made it without the help
of Kyusho-kun and his friends.
I am glad that everyone
is pleased, though.
Kinme-oneesan!
Oh, Nairo-chan! Good evening.
Good evening!
I'm sorry I couldn't stay to see
all of your rehearsal the other day.
That's okay!
You got busy washing
all of the happi coats for us!
Thank you!
Are you going to come
and see the parade tomorrow?
Yes, I think so. I'm planning
to come and watch after work.
Kinme-san!
Hey.
Look at you all! You really look the part!
Thanks, Kinme-san!
We hope you can come and see us in action!
Right, Kyu?
Uh... Yeah.
It is time once again for
the Kogashi Festival float competition!
Let's go win the wooden dashi category
once again this year!
Yeah!
Yeah, let's do it!
Let's get hyped up!
Wash It All Away
Here, Poly-chan.
Good morning, Kinme-san.
Come on in. Are you here to
pick up the suit? It's ready for you.
I'm so glad we have
good weather for the festival.
Yes.
So am I.
All right! All right!
Stop!
Heave-ho!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Heave-ho, heave-ho!
What?!
We are closed for the day.
Atami  Kogashi Festival Float Competition Judging Area
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Hey! Hey!
Atami
No.
Decorative Float Category/Designation
The Summer and the Festival Reunited!
Big Parade! Anniversary 25!
Shine On! The Starry Parade Miracle
Parade of the Hot Spring Floats
Clash of the Light and Water! Kogashi Wars Returns!
Utopia at the End of the Festival: Atami Fantasy Road
The Atami Onsen Monsters Are Here!
Hot Studs Reborn 2026!
Thirty-Six Views of Mt. Fuji: Big Wave in the Atami Ocean
Cheers to Atami! Lantern Fantasy!
Dance of Fire! The Atsuo Firestorm!
Summertime Steam-Blasting Dragon!
It's the Kogashi Festival Lantern Float!
Shine Brightly! Blossom Proudly!
Ready to Sail into a New Age! Children Are Atami's Treasure
Summer Cherry Blossoms in Full Bloom in Atami!
Atami Onsen Avengers: Save the World with Hot Water
Kinme-san.
Oh, Nairo-chan's grandmother?
Good evening!
Aren't the floats wonderful this year?
Yes!
Hurray! Hurray!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Look, it's Nairo and the kids!
Nairo, you're doing great!
Nairo-chan!
Heave-ho!
Hey!
Yeah!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
They're all going to have
such fond memories of this night,
wearing the happi coats I washed for them.
Heave-ho!
Oh, Kinme-san! Yoo-hoo!
What?
For some reason, I have a feeling...
this night will become
a fond memory for me as well.
Oh!
Hello, you two.
Whoa, nice timing!
Why doncha help us
pull the float, Kinme-san?
Huh?
We're about to turn around and go back.
Uh, is that all right?
Of course!
And how about a beer as thanks?
Uh... I'd better not drink.
You sure? Anyway, come and join in!
Okay!
Kinme-san, take this.
It's from our neighborhood association.
Oh... all right!
Here we go! Ready and...
One, two! One, two!
Nice work, guys!
Thanks! I'm beat!
Oh! Great job, folks!
Hello! You were all great today!
Oh, it's Kinme-san again. You too!
Yeah, really!
Wait, you don't have a beer?
I'm not much of a drinker.
Okay, so, what did you think?
Didn't I look cool up there?
I really got into it!
Yes, you all looked very cool,
way up on the top of the float like that.
Very impressive!
Aw, man! You seriously
thought I looked cool?
Kuriru-chan, Moruda-kun,
could I borrow you a sec?
I mean, you really inspired me, Kinme-san.
Hey, let's go.
Just call me Moruda, lord of the float!
What are you mumbling about anyway?
Would you like to get on the float?
Huh?
What? Is that all right?
With a mask on, nobody will know it's you.
Should be no problem at all.
Let's go.
I really hope this is okay.
You can use that ladder to get up.
Uh, all right!
Oh, I'd better put the mask on first.
Huh?
Watch out!
Kinme-san! Kyu! Are you okay?
Did you tell her to climb on?
Don't you know how dangerous that is?
Sorry.
Are you really okay, Kyu?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Thank goodness.
Are you sure you aren't injured?
I'm all right.
But I am a little embarrassed
for causing such a fuss.
I'm so sorry, Kinme-san.
Oh, no. It was my fault too.
U-Um, I'm really not hurt at all, so...
Kyusho-kun risked his neck to catch you.
Just what were you thinking?
I said I'm sorry.
Kinme-san's never done this before.
You've got to keep an eye on her!
Yeah, uh, I just...
This could have been a lot worse!
Kyusho-kun, thank you very much.
Huh? Uh... sure.
Kinme-san, I really am so sorry.
Honestly, I'm not hurt at all,
so please don't worry about it.
Translation:
Editing and Typesetting:
Michael Arnold
Ashley Barboza
Quality Control:
Translation Check:
Riley Dalton
Sriram Gurunathan
You were wonderful up there!
We were all so impressed!
I'm all burnt out.
Episode 6
Pop, Pop, Boom
Next time is "Pop, Pop, Boom."